

ANTON CERNEAVSCHII

UNITY DEVELOPER

PERSONAL DATA

Good day, My name is Anton and I'm a Unity game developer with over a 3 years experience. I have experience in working with 2D, 3D development in a Unity, from hyper-casual to casual and midcore.

Very self-motivated programmer with a great desire to develop and strive for the heights of the gaming industry.

SKILLS

- Android/IOS/PC development.
- Multiplayer development (Photon PUN, Fusion, Netcode for GameObject, Lobby, Relavl.
- Experience with architectures and cores based on Zenject (and others D containers), ECS.
- Worked with unit testing
- 5. Experience with working with asynchronous code Jobs system
- Experience with architect and creating custom packages, flexible and easy animations-control systems based on DoTween.
- 7. Experience with procedural mesh
- Making Shaders knowledges using Shader Graph, understanding of render systems.
- AR systems development experience
 C, C++, SFML, microprocessors development experience.

11. HTML CSS JavaScript experience

CONTACT INFORMATION

email: cherneavschii.anton@gmail.com linkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/anton-cernyavskiy-8a7995209/

WORK EXPERIENCE

Unity Developer Blue Gravity Studios (2022 - 2023)

Working with midcore projects, with full development cycle.
Creating game architecture.
Working with ECS, DI (Zenject).
Development of "ultiplayer core (based on NetCode for GameObjects

Unity Developer TryMyGames SRL (2021 - 2022)

2D, 3D Unity development.
Hyper casual games, casual games development.
Game Creating full cycle management.
Various plugins, assets for game development.
Working with procedural meshes, splines, Zenject, ECS.
Working with Shaders based on Shader Graph.

Unity Developer

Midnight Works (2020-2021)

3D development in a Unity.

Multiplayer based on Photon PUN.

Hyper casual games android/iOS development.

Casual games development.

Procedural mesh generation, creating basic shaders, various. pluginsfor Unity, algorithms, many different assets.

EDUCATION

Technical University of Moldova Biomedical engineer

Licence - 2019 - 2023

INTERESTS AND HOBBIES

I love coffee, music, mathematics, physics, programming.

WORK EXAMPLES

Dive into projects created with my linkedIn profile:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/anton-cernyavskiy-8a7995209/details/projects/